PROFESSOR: OK, so today we're
going to talk about search.
And the key idea with search is that
we're going to want to be able to
build good agents that
make good decisions.
And in order to make good decisions in
general, you have to plan ahead.
So today we're going to think about what
it means to have an agent that
plans ahead and thinks about the
consequences of its actions, so they
can use those consequences to make a
good decision in the first place.
We're going to formalize this idea of
planning ahead as a search problem.
And then we're going to talk about
how to solve search problems.
And we'll begin with uninformed
search methods.
And this will include depth-first
and breadth-first search and
uniform cost search.
And we'll be looking all of these in a
common context so that we can see them
and compare them to the search methods
we're going to get later, where we're
going to have not uninformed search,
but search guided by a heuristic.